[{"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " we need to talk to you about something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yeah. we don't feel like we can host thanksgiving this year.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " are you kidding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " well, it's just with uhm, work and the stress of adoption, we just don't feel like we have the energy. plus, we don't think it's fair that every year the burden falls on us.", "answer": "  that doesn't sound like you... that's monica talking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no, no! we made this decision together.", "answer": " she's putting words in your mouth!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " don't you put words in people's mouths, you put turkey in people's mouths!", "answer": " i can't believe this! this is emma's first thanksgiving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " no, it's not!", "answer": " it's not?  when was she born?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well, personally i think it's great you're giving yourself a break.", "answer": " thank you, pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " sure. it's just as well... i mean, last year wasn't very good. i think she's losing her touch.", "answer": " what? you are way off, lady!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " am i? really? am i? well, why don't you cook thanksgiving dinner and prove me wrong! well, think about it, think about it, you'll be trying to top than you did last year. you'd be in competition... with yourself.", "answer": " that's my favourite kind! okay, we are doing this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " don't let yourself get manipulated this way!", "answer": " hey, stay out of this, chandler! this is between me... and me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi! happy thanksgiving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh, yeah, happy needless-turkey-murder day.", "answer": " you guys, i ordered some chocolate pies from that bakery on bleecker. could you pick them up for me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " you're not making the pies yourself?", "answer": " no, no, no, i don't make chocolate pies. when i was younger i-i enter in this pie-eating contest. i ate so many that just the thought of them made me sick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " did you at least win the contest?", "answer": " 2 minutes, 12 pies and a part of one tin! okay, i see you guys at 4.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " can't wait!", "answer": " this dinner is gonna be so great! in your face, last year &quot;me&quot;!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey rach.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what's emma doing today?", "answer": " well, let's see... uh... i know that she has a meeting with her lawyer and then she has to make a very big poop. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " well, i wanna enter her in a baby beauty pageant.", "answer": " oh my god! that's the creepiest thing i've ever heard!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " okay, but, well, before you say no, my friend susanne is entering her kid and compared to emma she's a real dog!", "answer": " oh! phoebe, all babies are beautiful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  oh... okay.", "answer": " phoebe, just the idea of pitting one baby against another, i mean, you know, and judging who's cuter just for a trophy...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " and a thousand dollars.", "answer": " ...is something i'm very interested in! oh please, do not tell ross. he still believes that  what's in the inside is important...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " okay, oh, and emma needs a cowgirl outfit for the competition.", "answer": " where am i gonna get a cowgirl outfit on thanksgiving?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well, i was thinking...", "answer": " oh, take the clothes of joey's cabbage patch kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  did someone drop the baton again?", "answer": " why come all the way from kansas to do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  i don't get older. i just get better!", "answer": " you know what just occurred to me? this could be our last thanksgiving just the two of us. i mean, we could be getting a baby soon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " you don't know that.", "answer": " somebody is gonna pick us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " yeah, but we haven't heard a thing from the adoption agency and it has been weeks!", "answer": " i'm telling ya! it's gonna happen. next year it's gonna be you, me and the little hemingway bing.  what, he's my favourite author!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " name one of his books.", "answer": "  &quot;the firm&quot;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " ok, let's see... uhm, okay, the turkey is in the oven, the stuffing is ready...", "answer": " you know, you always cook this meal all by yourself. let me help this year.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, chandler, that's sweet. but you don't have to do everything doctor phil tells you to do.", "answer": " i'm serious, let me do something, just not the turkey or the stuffing, nothing &quot;high profile&quot;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " ok, let's see... oh, the cranberry sauce, it is easy to make and no-one really cares about it.", "answer": " tell me more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey! hey, guess what joey has!", "answer": " three tickets to today's rangers game!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " dude, i wanted him to guess.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " yeah, they're great seats too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " guess where they are?", "answer": " center ice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " did i do something to you?", "answer": " hmm, the game's at one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " dinner is at four, we'll never gonna make it back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " so we'll leave before it's over, we'll be back in time.", "answer": " you say that now, but it could take us a long time to get back home. plus joey could get lost and and they could have to page us to go pick him up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " dude, two times that happened!", "answer": " look, monica has been working hard all day, she didn't wanna host this thing in the first place, we shouldn't go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " he's right, man.", "answer": " right, i guess. alright, so see you at four.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay.  and get ready to taste my very special cranberries. or should i say... chanberries!", "answer": " that's some gentle comedy, dude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " we're still going at the game, right?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " this is contestant number sixteen, rebecca...", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh phoebe, listen. well, i think we gotta go. this place is really freaking me out. i've been watching this guy over there, i don't think he came with a kid!", "answer": " we can't leave now! there was this one baby, haley, who was favourite to win and she got croup, so she had to stay home! this competition just blew wide open, folks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " phoebe, i think... it's just too weird, i just saw a one year old running around with pantyhose on!", "answer": " oh, i know, we should have been more prepared.  it's okay. now, the way i see it, our real competition now is cameron. oh my god, they just took her sweater off. look at those arms! hello michelin man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh, phoebe! come on! you know what, it's already three o'clock and they haven't even gotten to emma's group yet. we gotta go, we got dinner!", "answer": "  but emma's got what it takes, she could go all the way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " phoebe, you have to calm down.", "answer": " okay. rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area are in this room right now! i overheard one of the judges say that not one of them holds a candle to emma!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " you heard them say that?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " all right, okay. alright, let's give to these babies something to cry about!", "answer": " good! oh yay! let's get down to business! emma needs some makeup!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " no, what?", "answer": " well, she's gonna look all washed out next to the other contestants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no phoebe, i am not letting you put makeup on my baby!", "answer": " why not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " oh, bob, get off the guy!", "answer": " oh! what a game, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i know, yeah.", "answer": " i can't believe chandler is missing this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah. i am sorry he's not here too, but i got to say,  i am really enjoying nacho chair.", "answer": " yeah, i'd probably enjoy it more if you didn't keep batting my hand away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " ohhhh! these seats are great!", "answer": " i know, i know! when i was here for holidays on ice  i was sitting so far away michelle kwan couldn't read my banner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  wow, hey, we'd better get going. if we don't leave right now, we'll be late for dinner.", "answer": " oh, but it's a kind game! so we're a little late, you know, the girls will be there, let's stay just for one more goal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i don't know...", "answer": " one more fight!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " where is everybody? they're forty-five minutes late!", "answer": " i can't believe they are not here! i slave and i slave for what? they've ruined cranberry day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " how late are we?", "answer": " forty-five minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  here!", "answer": " okay. rachel and phoebe are already there, okay? so they probably started without us. we could just slip in and no-one needs to know where we were!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you may want to lose the foam finger!", "answer": " oh, no, no, no, no, no. you just want to put it on your hand!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " you are not at thanksgiving?", "answer": " no...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " no, we're late!", "answer": " what are you doing here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " don't point that thing at me, tribbiani!", "answer": " so, nobody's here? monica's gonna kill us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah, where were you!", "answer": " yeah, yeah, what's with the trophy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " uh, we were at the spelling bee!", "answer": " and i won!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " you won an adult thanksgiving day spelling bee.", "answer": " yes!  y-e-s. yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " let me see this...  grand supreme little darling, new york division.", "answer": " yeah. that's me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " you entered emma into a beauty pageant?", "answer": " and it looks like she put makeup on her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " wait a second, wait a second, where have i seen that cowgirl outfit before...", "answer": " i can't believe this, she's our daughter! that you would treat her like some kind of showdog is inexcusable!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " she won a thousand dollars!", "answer": " so this is an annual thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  oh! that's alicia mae emory's outfit!", "answer": " you guys, there are people in there who are not getting any happier!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yeah. what are we gonna do?", "answer": " well, i don't know, you guys figure it out, i got to put emma down for a nap.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " all right. hey rach, while you're in there, throw something on alicia mae.", "answer": " alright, what are we gonna say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ooh, we'll say that we were mugged! you can't get mad at someone who's been mugged!", "answer": " oh, good, that's good, but you don't look like you were mugged!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  they're out there!", "answer": " ohhh! let me see! oh god, i can't believe this! they're an hour late and they're just staying out there, talking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  everything is so distorted! looks like joey has a giant hand! which says &quot;rangers&quot; on it. they went to the game!", "answer": "  oooh! they are in for a world of pain!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  ross' shirt is torn.", "answer": " oh! they're late and they're sloppy!  (rachel comes out of her apartment}", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " alright, emma is napping...  what happened to your shirt?", "answer": " i got mugged. and they stole my pocket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " we're just... we're trying to figure out an excuse. hey! ooh! how about this: we can say that monica told us 5 o'clock, not 4 o'clock. that way we're right on time!  or... or, we can plant pcp in the apartment and call the cops on her.", "answer": "  that would be a good way to get rid of all the pcp we have lying around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, god. this is bad. this is so bad.", "answer": " well, let's just go in there and face them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " well, i'm not going in first. i bet that vein on monica's forehead is popping like crazy.", "answer": " i hate that thing, it's like a... bolt of lightning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " oh, hey, i have an idea. why don't we play rock-paper-scissors, and whoever loses goes in first.  ready? .", "answer": "  ah-haah! i win!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " what is that?", "answer": " that's fire. beats everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh, really? does it beat water balloon? .", "answer": " ooh! well played, phoebe buffay, well played.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " alright, enough, enough, come on. let's just all go in at the same time.", "answer": " alright, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " it's locked.", "answer": " wha...? oh sure, now they lock it, but when they're having sex on the couch, its like: &quot;come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy&quot;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no! everything's cold. the turkey's dried out and the... the stuffing is all soggy.", "answer": " yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that...  what happens to cranberry sauce?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  nothing. it's fine.", "answer": "  oh thank god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " come on you guys, we're sorry, alri...? our subway broke down.", "answer": "  that's a lie, you went to the game, i can see joey's hand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " how are we gonna decide who gets this?", "answer": "  water balloon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " what are we gonna do? i'm starving.", "answer": "  oh, i just remembered. we do have something to eat. monica put something in our oven this morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " hey, you touch that and you will be sorry.", "answer": " guys, i'd listen to her. the vein is bigger than i've ever seen it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " ha-ha! all you got was monica's stinky brussels sprouts!", "answer": " stinky?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh, i know... i still have my old key!  we can just unlock the door.", "answer": " well, i don't know if that's such a good idea. they clearly don't want to be with us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  just get in there and make a face to face apology, you know? look them in the eye. i know i can get them to forgive us.", "answer": " i don't know...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i'm telling ya...  i can do it.", "answer": "   yeah, he can do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " the cranberries...?", "answer": " oh! enough! a monkey could have made 'em!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": "  hey listen guys, we feel really terrible.", "answer": " he's doing that weird eye contact thing. don't look at him, don't look at him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i feel terrible. phoebe and rachel: so, so sorry.", "answer": "  now let's not ruin this day. you worked so hard. let's move past this and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " the floating heads do make a good point.", "answer": " yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " so bad.", "answer": " so bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " so bad.", "answer": "  okay, okay. you two  go get the dessert. and i'll let you in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " dessert?", "answer": " yeah, i asked you and phoebe to pick up the pies. you did remember, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " grand supreme little darling?", "answer": " congratulatioooons!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh my god! you forgot the pies? well, i cannot believe this. you force me to make dinner, then you're an hour late and you forget the one little thing that i asked you to do.", "answer": " really girls, not cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " well, you manheads aren't any better. you lied about going to the game. you knew it would make you late, and you still went anyway.", "answer": " hey! i'm getting a little tired of this okay? we said we're sorry. it's thanksgiving for pete's sakes! a day of forgiveness!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " it's a day to be thankful.", "answer": "  don't make me come up there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " it's too late for apologies.", "answer": " fine! let's just go. i don't need your stupid dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " that would be a lot more convincing if you weren't drooling.", "answer": " ewww, is that what that is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " sorry!", "answer": " come on you guys, let's just do our own thanksgiving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " yeah! i'll cook!", "answer": " yeah! let's go out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " yeah! you three have a nice thanksgiving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " the three of us?", "answer": " yeah! you, chan, and the vein!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " oh-oh! i'm stuck!", "answer": " joey, that is not gonna work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " no seriously... i'm really wedged in here.", "answer": " i'll pull you through.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": "  aaw-ahhh-aaahhh stop! stop! i'm worried about damaging my head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " a little late for that.", "answer": " alright, hurry up, you gotta do something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " alright, well, this does not change anything.  okay, we need to get something to grease the sides of his face.", "answer": " uhm, we've got turkey grease.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " bring it.", "answer": " i just wanna say that i'm sorry i referred to the vein as a seperate person...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay, try it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " it isn't working.", "answer": " alright, we're gonna have to unscrew the chain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " well hurry, i can't feel my ears!", "answer": " can you ever feel your ears?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " interesting...", "answer": " chandler, where are your tools?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": "  oh, i left them on my bulldozer... i don't have tools!", "answer": " i do, but rachel borrowed them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " i lent them to ross.", "answer": " i gave them to joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " i left them at the park.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": "  i'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.", "answer": " i've already stuffed a bunch of brussel sprouts down his pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " okay, i have to get that. now when i get back, i want you and your friends to be gone. thanksgiving is over. the vein has spoken.", "answer": " it's really starting to hurt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " okay, look, i'm gonna pull on the door and you guys push as hard as you can. maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay? okay, so push!", "answer": " just a sec., we're kind in the middle of something here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " ooh! stop putting things down my pants!", "answer": " come on guys, push!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " my cranberries!", "answer": "  man, i've got food all over me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 341, "asentId": 342}, {"question": "  look! look! look what the... look what... look what the floating heads did!", "answer": "  i don't care.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " what's going on?", "answer": " that was the adoption agency...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": " and?", "answer": " we're getting a baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}, {"question": " i'm so happy for you!", "answer": " this thanksgiving kicks last thanksgiving's ass!  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " to monica and chandler... and that knocked up girl in ohio.", "answer": " i'm just so happy you guys are finally getting a kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": " i know. have you considered pageanting?", "answer": " i can't believe they called, and we're actually getting a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 359, "asentId": 360}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " sure. i went through the exact same thing with alicia mae emory... the waiting, the wandering... then one day... i get that call from toys &quot;r&quot; us... she was in stock!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep8.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}]